♪ IT'S BEEN A LONG DAY WITHOUT YOU, MY FRIEND ♪
♪ FOI UM LONGO DIA SEM VOCÊ, MEU AMIGO ♪
♪ AND I'LL TELL YOU ALL ABOUT IT WHEN I SEE YOU AGAIN ♪
♪ E EU TE CONTAREI TUDO SOBRE ISSO QUANDO TE VER DE NOVO ♪
♪ WE'VE COME A LONG WAY FROM WHERE WE BEGAN ♪
♪ NÓS PERCORREMOS UM LONGO CAMINHO DE ONDE COMEÇAMOS ♪
♪ OH, I'LL TELL YOU ALL ABOUT IT WHEN I SEE YOU AGAIN ♪
♪ OH, EU TE CONTAREI TUDO SOBRE ISSO QUANDO TE VER DE NOVO ♪
♪ WHEN I SEE YOU AGAIN ♪
♪ QUANDO EU TE VER DE NOVO ♪
♪ [ Rapping ] DAMN, WHO KNEW ALL THE PLANES WE FLEW ♪
♪ [ ******* ] CARAMBA, QUEM SABIA DE TODOS OS AVIÕES QUE VOAMOS ♪
♪ GOOD THINGS WE BEEN THROUGH ♪
♪ COISAS BOAS PELAS QUAIS PASSAMOS ♪
♪ THAT I'D BE STANDING RIGHT HERE ♪
♪ QUE EU ESTARIA BEM AQUI ♪
♪ TALKING TO YOU 'BOUT ANOTHER PATH ♪
♪ FALANDO COM VOCÊ SOBRE OUTRO CAMINHO ♪
♪ I KNOW WE LOVED TO HIT THE ROAD AND LAUGH ♪
♪ EU SEI QUE AMAMOS PEGAR A ESTRADA E RIR ♪
♪ BUT SOMETHING TOLD ME THAT IT WOULDN'T LAST ♪
♪ MAS ALGO ME DISSE QUE NÃO IRIA DURAR ♪
♪ HAD TO SWITCH UP, LOOK AT THINGS DIFFERENT ♪
♪ TIVE QUE MUDAR, OLHAR PARA AS COISAS DE FORMA DIFERENTE ♪
♪ SEE THE BIGGER PICTURE ♪
♪ VEJA O QUADRO GERAL ♪
♪ THOSE WERE THE DAYS, HARD WORK FOREVER PAYS ♪
♪ ESSES ERA OS DIAS, TRABALHO DURO PARA SEMPRE COMPENSA ♪
♪ NOW I SEE YOU IN A BETTER PLACE ♪
♪ AGORA TE VEJO EM UM LUGAR MELHOR ♪
♪ SEE YOU IN A BETTER PLACE ♪
♪ TE VEJO EM UM LUGAR MELHOR ♪
♪ UNH ♪
♪ UNH ♪
♪ HOW COULD WE NOT TALK ABOUT FAMILY ♪
♪ COMO PODEMOS NÃO FALAR SOBRE FAMÍLIA ♪
♪ WHEN FAMILY'S ALL THAT WE GOT? ♪
♪ QUANDO FAMÍLIA É TUDO O QUE TEMOS? ♪
♪ EVERYTHING I WENT THROUGH ♪
♪ TUDO QUE EU PASSEI ♪
♪ YOU WERE STANDING THERE BY MY SIDE ♪
♪ VOCÊ ESTAVA LÁ DO MEU LADO ♪
♪ AND NOW YOU GON' BE WITH ME FOR THE LAST RIDE ♪
♪ E AGORA VOCÊ VAI FICAR COMIGO NA ÚLTIMA VIAGEM ♪
♪ IT'S BEEN A LONG DAY WITHOUT YOU, MY FRIEND ♪
♪ FOI UM LONGO DIA SEM VOCÊ, MEU AMIGO ♪
♪ AND I'LL TELL YOU ALL ABOUT IT WHEN I SEE YOU AGAIN ♪
♪ E EU VOU TE CONTAREI TUDO SOBRE ISSO QUANDO TE VER DE NOVO ♪
I'LL SEE YOU AGAIN.
TE VEREI DE NOVO.
♪ WE'VE COME A LONG WAY ♪
♪ NÓS PERCORREMOS MUITO ♪
CAME A LONG WAY.
PERCORREMOS MUITO LONGO.
♪ FROM WHERE WE BEGAN ♪
♪ DE ONDE COMEÇAMOS ♪
♪ OH, I'LL TELL YOU ALL ABOUT IT WHEN I SEE YOU AGAIN ♪
♪ OH,EU TE CONTAREI TUDO SOBRE ISSO QUANDO TE VER DE NOVO ♪
LET ME TELL YOU.
DEIXA EU TE CONTAR.
♪ WHEN I SEE YOU AGAIN ♪
♪ QUANDO EU TE VER DE NOVO ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH-OH-OH-OH ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH-OH-OH-OH ♪
♪ OOH-OOH-OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH ♪
♪ OOH-OOH-OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH ♪
♪ OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH-OOH-OOH ♪
♪ OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH-OOH-OOH ♪
♪ OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH-OOH ♪
♪ OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH-OOH ♪
[ Rapping ] ♪ FIRST, YOU BOTH GO OUT YOUR WAY ♪
[ ******* ] ♪ PRIMEIRO, VOCÊS DOIS SAEM DO SEU JEITO ♪
♪ AND THE VIBE IS FEELING STRONG ♪
♪ E A VIBE ESTÁ PARECER FORTE ♪
♪ AND WHAT'S SMALL TURNED TO A FRIENDSHIP ♪
♪ E O QUE É PEQUENO SE TRANSFORMOU EM UMA AMIZADE ♪
♪ A FRIENDSHIP TURNED TO A BOND ♪
♪ UMA AMIZADE SE TRANSFORMOU EM UM VÍNCULO ♪
♪ AND THAT BOND WILL NEVER BE BROKEN ♪
♪ E ESSE VÍNCULO NUNCA SERÁ QUEBRADO ♪
♪ THE LOVE WILL NEVER GET LOST ♪
♪ O AMOR NUNCA SE PERDERÁ ♪
♪ AND THE LOVE WILL NEVER GET LOST ♪
♪ E O AMOR NUNCA SE PERDERÁ ♪
♪ AND WHEN BROTHERHOOD COME FIRST ♪
♪ E QUANDO A IRMANDADE VEM PRIMEIRO ♪
♪ THEN THE LINE WILL NEVER BE CROSSED ♪
♪ ENTÃO A LINHA NUNCA SERÁ CRUZADA ♪
♪ ESTABLISHED IT ON OUR OWN ♪
♪ A ESTABELECEMOS POR NÓS MESMOS ♪
♪ WHEN THAT LINE HAD TO BE DRAWN ♪
♪ QUANDO ESSA LINHA TINHA QUE SER TRAÇADA ♪
♪ AND THAT LINE IS WHAT WE REACHED ♪
♪ E ESSA LINHA FOI ONDE ALCANÇAMOS ♪
♪ SO REMEMBER ME WHEN I'M GONE ♪
♪ ENTÃO LEMBRE-SE DE MIM QUANDO EU FOR ♪
♪ REMEMBER ME WHEN I'M GONE ♪
♪ LEMBRE-SE DE MIM QUANDO EU FOR ♪
♪ HOW COULD WE NOT TALK ABOUT FAMILY ♪
♪ COMO PODEMOS NÃO FALAR SOBRE FAMÍLIA ♪
♪ WHEN FAMILY'S ALL THAT WE GOT? ♪
♪ QUANDO FAMÍLIA É TUDO O QUE TEMOS? ♪
♪ EVERYTHING I WENT THROUGH ♪
♪ TUDO QUE EU PASSEI ♪
♪ YOU WERE STANDING THERE BY MY SIDE ♪
♪ VOCÊ ESTAVA LÁ DO MEU LADO ♪
♪ AND NOW YOU GON' BE WITH ME FOR THE LAST RIDE ♪
♪ E AGORA VOCÊ VAI FICAR COMIGO NA ÚLTIMA VIAGEM ♪
♪ LET THE LIGHT GUIDE YOUR WAY ♪
♪ DEIXE A LUZ GUIAR SEU CAMINHO ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ SIM ♪
♪ HOLD EVERY MEMORY AS YOU GO ♪
♪ GUARDE CADA MEMÓRIA CONFORME VOCÊ ANDA ♪
♪ AND EVERY ROAD YOU TAKE ♪
♪ E CADA ESTRADA QUE VOCÊ PEGA ♪
♪ WILL ALWAYS LEAD YOU HOME ♪
♪ SEMPRE TE LEVARÁ PARA CASA ♪
♪ HOME ♪
♪ CASA ♪
♪ IT'S BEEN A LONG DAY WITHOUT YOU, MY FRIEND ♪
♪ FOI UM LONGO DIA SEM VOCÊ, MEU AMIGO ♪
♪ AND I'LL TELL YOU ALL ABOUT IT WHEN I SEE YOU AGAIN ♪
♪ E EU VOU TE CONTAR TUDO SOBRE ISSO QUANDO EU TE VER DE NOVO ♪
♪ WE'VE COME A LONG WAY FROM WHERE WE BEGAN ♪
♪ NÓS PERCORREMOS MUITO DE ONDE COMEÇAMOS ♪
♪ OH, I'LL TELL YOU ALL ABOUT IT WHEN I SEE YOU AGAIN ♪
♪ OH, EU VOU TE CONTAR TUDO SOBRE ISSO QUANDO EU TE VER DE NOVO ♪
♪ WHEN I SEE YOU AGAIN ♪
♪ QUANDO EU TE VER DE NOVO ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH-OH-OH-OH ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH-OH-OH-OH ♪
♪ OOH-OOH-OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH ♪
♪ OOH-OOH-OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH ♪
♪ OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH-OOH-OOH ♪
♪ OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH-OOH-OOH ♪
♪ OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH-OOH ♪
♪ OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH-OOH ♪
♪ WHEN I SEE YOU AGAIN ♪
♪ QUANDO EU TE VER DE NOVO ♪
♪ SEE YOU AGAIN ♪
♪ TE VER DE NOVO ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH-OH-OH ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH-OH-OH ♪
♪ OOH-OOH-OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH ♪
♪ OOH-OOH-OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH ♪
♪ OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH-OOH-OOH ♪
♪ OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH-OOH-OOH ♪
♪ OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH-OOH ♪
♪ OOH-OOH, OOH-OOH-OOH ♪
♪ WHEN I SEE YOU AGAIN ♪
♪ QUANDO EU TE VER DE NOVO ♪